Jen beat him on purpose for the championship!
Yeah!
What is this?
She beat him on purpose?
Here is the next penalty game!
Boiling water on your stomach.
That's worse than cold.
Here, take this card.
One more time.
And this one.
Here we go!
One more time.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Who is it?
Who?
I'm here.
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I
Who was that you were all pointing at?
Japanese people talking.
Oh, no.
Finally.
Uemiso.
Let's start from the vortex.
I'll go the other way around.
Yes, sir.
Well, the first move is, I'll just do it.
First move...
Yes, sir.
I'm scared... I'm scared...
You just said that.
You're not hesitating anymore... like Jiro.
No, it doesn't.
It's like you're smiling like you're free of everything.
No, no, no, no, no.
Maybe he's making the most of what he just said.
He's making the most of it.
It's good. It's good.
That's good.
Hakkeshi.
Forgive me.
Oh, I'm scared.
Oh, I'm going.
I'm going.
I'm in!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm here, just in case.
You're trying so hard to be the joker.
No, I'm not.
You're back.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just lost my turn.
It's definitely like this now.
There's nothing in the middle.
Oh, it's stuck.
Oh, but it works.
I can do it.
I can't.
It's gone!
No, but I still feel like I can do it.
Please don't struggle.
It doesn't feel so wobbly.
But, you know, surprisingly, there's no middle anymore.
It's just not solid.
Can I go?
Go wherever you want.
Let's go.
I think it's time to make it one, two.
Two.
We have to go on the offensive.
Here it is.
They're really aggressive.
It's suspicious.
Like trying to make one from earlier.
He's speeding up.
He's really aggressive.
I doubt it.
He's been trying to get one since a while ago.
His speed has increased.
Seriousness.
Which is it?
Large.
I can afford to be here.
Nice.
The middle.
There's no middle.
There's no middle ground.
Who's the best liar in the room?
We're talking.
Who is the best liar?
Let's talk.
One more time,
Who is the best liar?
Let's talk.
One more time,
Elena, we were all talking today,
Who can tell the best lies?
Who can lie the best about these lies?
What do you think? What do you think?
What do you think?
You ashamed?
Hmmm...
I think there might be quite a few cuts of Moeka in today's show.
You're funny today, too.
But there's a cut at home, too.
You're funny.
What, that one we did before, the one with the last ant?
What? No.
I didn't put it there.
Gendered and peppered.
Wow!
But home is also a cut.
Oh, it's funny.
But you know, I think you guys are really good at lying.
I mean, they're good at lying, but they're good at doing it without a care in the world.
Don't be like that.
Yuzu is always moving people's minds.
Sometimes they're right.
I don't know.
On the contrary, I don't know.
That's why I'm always the most suspicious.
What?
Let's look for them one at a time.
There's only two of them, for what it's worth.
Oh, you can't?
No, you can't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Yes, you can.
More of these.
Oh, oh.
Who put this one here?
Yuzu, right?
Oh, yuzu.
And now this one. And now the discovery.
That's weird.
Don't do that, it's definitely not scary.
It's not scary at all.
Yuzu in places.
You're getting on my nerves.
Not in places.
100%.
All of it.
Hanya? I don't like it. My mom says that a lot, too.
Oh no. I'm always mad at her.
Maybe I shouldn't say that to her. No, it might really be invincible.
Maybe I shouldn't say "Airabama" at all. Yeah, if you say it like we do,
I can tell that you might be doing it on purpose. Even if Airabama does it, he's doing it.
He's already doing it. He's doing it. It's not there. It's not here, but wait a minute.
Oops. I've always been pretty extreme. That's weird.
Oh, you don't have it? I'd like to go extreme. Yeah, you can't? I'd like to go to the extreme.
Where is it? I want it to be radical.
I want it to be radical.
They just said radical the first time, and now I'm being set up.
I'm hooked.